## Aman Raj

### Software Engineer (Mobile Apps/Frontend)

Software Engineer (Fronted/Mobile Apps) having 2 years of professional and 6 months of internship experience in development. Working in App Dev team (DWS) at Unisys. Tech used are React Native, Native Android and IOS for app development.







in linkedin.com/in/aman-raj-194363180

#### 9952908249

- amanraj.co.in/
- github.com/amanraj0505

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Engineer(Mobile Apps/Frontend)** Unisys India.

09/2020 - Present Bengaluru

Frontend Developer (Mobile Application Team)

- Working under App Dev team under Unisys DWS (Intelliserve), using technologies like react native, core android.
- Worked on API integration team that handles the integration, development, deployment and publishing of backend API that powers Inteliserve Platform.

Contact: www.unisys.com

## Android Development Intern

Sensen Networks

02/2020 - 07/2020 Hyderabad

Core Android Team

 Worked in the App Development Team helping with the implementation of several networking and app features with Native Android using Core JAVA.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelors In Technology (Computer Science And Engineering)

SRM Institute Of Science And Technology, Chennai

05/2016 - 05/2020 8.8 CGPA

Courses

 Computer Science And Engineering Major

# **Senior Secondary Education**Birla School Pilani, Pilani (Rajasthan)

04/2014 - 04/2015 93%

Courses

Science

### **SKILLS**



# PERSONAL/ PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS

Portfolio Website (06/2021 - Present)

Personal Website: <a href="https://amanraj.co.in">https://amanraj.co.in</a>

Notescape (09/2021 - Present)

- Minimal/Secure/Offline Note taking app made using react native, redux, javascript etc.
- Published on PLAY STORE: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.notescape

#### Inteliapp By Unisys (08/2021 - Present)

- Extensive configurable Enterprise App made from react native, that can be configured remotely according to a client's need. The app is also used to integrate Unisys Enterprise Personal Assistant chat with mobile.
- APPLE APP STORE: https://apps.apple.com/in/app/inteliapp-one-app/id1567441535
- GOOGLE PLAY STORE: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.unisys.onemobileapp

React Notes (08/2021 - Present)

- Notes App Using React.js
- APP: <a href="https://notes.amanraj.co.in/">https://notes.amanraj.co.in/</a>

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

## CLIENT-CENTRICITY (Awarded By Unisys) (03/2021 - Present)

Word Of Manager/ Teammates :You have demonstrated quick learning on new technology areas and played an important role in multiple client implementations like DJO, Avianca, Baxter and ISA. We appreciate your proactiveness and strong technical skills.

#### CURIOSITY (Awarded By Unisys) (09/2021 - Present)

Manager: Congratulations on your exemplary contributions towards the development of InteliApp-oneApp. You have demonstrated quick learning and moving from PoC to implementation with great agility.